(trumpet fanfare music)
(energetic hip hop music)
♪ Pack it up, pack it in, let me begin ♪
♪ I came to win, battle me that's a sin ♪
♪ I won't ever slack up,
punk you better back up ♪
♪ Try and play the role and
yo the whole crew'll act up ♪
♪ Get up, stand up c'mon,
throw your hands up ♪
♪ If you've got the feeling,
jump across the ceiling ♪
♪ Muggs lifts a funk flow,
someone's talking junk ♪
♪ Yo I bust him in the eye ♪
♪ And then I'll take the punk's hoe ♪
♪ Feelin', funkin', amps in the
trunk and I got more rhymes ♪
♪ Than there's cops at
a Dunkin' Donuts shop ♪
♪ Sho' nuff, I got props ♪
♪ From the kids on the hill
plus my mom and my pops ♪
♪ I came to get down, I came to get down ♪
♪ So get out your seat and jump around ♪
♪ Jump around ♪
♪ Jump up, jump up and get down ♪
♪ Jump, jump, jump, jump, everybody jump ♪
♪ Jump, jump, jump, jump ♪
♪ Jump, jump, jump, jump, jump ♪
♪ I'll serve your ass like John McEnroe ♪
♪ If your girl steps up,
I'm smacking the hoe ♪
♪ Word to your moms,
I came to drop bombs ♪
♪ I got more rhymes than
the Bible's got Psalms ♪
♪ And just like the
Prodigal Son I've returned ♪
♪ Anyone stepping to
me you'll get burned ♪
♪ 'Cause I got lyrics,
but you ain't got none ♪
♪ If you come to battle bring a shotgun ♪
♪ But if you do you're a fool,
'cause I duel, to the death ♪
♪ Trying to step to me,
you'll take your last breath ♪
♪ I got the skills, come get your fill ♪
♪ 'Cause when I shoot the
gift, I shoot to kill ♪
♪ I came to get down, I came to get down ♪
♪ So get out your seat and jump around ♪
♪ Jump around ♪
♪ Jump up, jump up and get down ♪
♪ Jump, jump, jump, jump, everybody jump ♪
♪ Jump, jump, jump, jump ♪
♪ Jump, jump, jump, jump, jump ♪
♪ I'm the cream of the
crop, I rise to the top ♪
♪ I never eat a pig,
'cause a pig is a cop ♪
♪ Or better yet a Terminator,
like Arnold Schwarzenegger ♪
♪ Try to play me out like,
as if my name was Sega ♪
♪ But I ain't going out
like no punk bitch ♪
♪ Get used to one style
and yo and I might switch ♪
♪ It up up and around,
then buck buck you down ♪
♪ Put out your head and then you wake up ♪
♪ In the Dawn of the Dead ♪
♪ I'm coming to get ya,
I'm coming to get ya ♪
♪ Spitting out lyrics, homie I'll wet ya ♪
♪ I came to get down, I came to get down ♪
♪ So get out your seat and jump around ♪
♪ Jump around ♪
♪ Jump up, jump up and get down ♪
♪ Jump, jump, jump, jump, Everybody jump ♪
♪ Jump, jump, jump, jump ♪
♪ Jump, jump, jump, jump, everybody jump ♪
♪ Jump ♪
♪ Yo, this is dedicated
to Joe The Biter Nicolo ♪
♪ Grab your Bozack, punk ♪